qklnk.co 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | RhythmOne

For the Privacy Policy relating to RhythmOne products and services - click here.

For the Privacy Policy relating to RadiumOne products and services - click here.

For the Privacy Policy relating to YuMe Product and Services - [click here.](http://www.yume.com/yume-network-privacy-policy)

**RhythmOne Privacy Policy**

**LAST UPDATED May 23, 2018**

Unless otherwise indicated below, this privacy policy applies to any RhythmOne website, any RhythmOne service as well as any personal information RhythmOne may collect across partnered and unaffiliated sites.

RhythmOne (“RhythmOne” or “we” or “us”), is committed to protecting your (“your” or “you” or “user”) privacy. This privacy policy describes how RhythmOne collects and uses the personal information you provide as well as your rights in relation to such information.

**Data Collection of User Information**

RhythmOne collects information that does not directly identify you but that may include but not be limited to, the server you are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP you use, the type of browser you use, sites you have visited, products you have researched and your IP address. This information is obtained solely for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring a given ad's effectiveness on behalf of RhythmOne’s clients.

In addition, RhythmOne may engage third party providers such as Google Analytics to process the information described above but solely for purposes of monitoring user behavior on the site or service.

**Consumer Information**

RhythmOne is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and adheres to its Code of Conduct. RhythmOne does not collect or use "sensitive consumer information" (as defined in the NAI's Self-Regulatory Code of Conduct) in its online behavioral advertising activities and does not offer or sell to its clients segments based on sensitive consumer information. "Sensitive consumer information" includes social security numbers or other government-issued identifiers, insurance plan numbers, financial account numbers, information that describes the precise real-time geographic location of an individual derived through location-based services such as through GPS-enabled devices, and precise information about past, present, or potential future health or medical conditions or treatments, including genetic, genomic and family medical history. RhythmOne maintains internal policies and procedures designed to safeguard against the collection or use of such information.

**Legal basis for processing personal information (EEA Users only)**

If you are a User from the European Economic Area, our or our customer's legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect personal information from you only (i) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights, or (iii) where we have your consent to do so.

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information).

If we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), this interest will normally be to operate our platform and communicating with you as necessary to provide our services to you and for our legitimate commercial interest, for instance, when responding to your queries, improving our platform, undertaking marketing, or for the purposes of detecting or preventing illegal activities. We may have other legitimate interests and if appropriate we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting us” heading below.

**Opting Out of Cookies**

Opting Out of Cookies RhythmOne is a member of the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA), a cooperative of companies committed to building responsible advertising policies across the Internet, and adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. RhythmOne is also a member of the Network Advertising Imitative (NAI) and we adhere to NAI’s 2013 Code of Conduct. To learn more about interest-based or online behavioral advertising, and other advertising companies’ privacy policies and opt-out, please visit the DAA Website - <http://www.aboutads.info/>. You can opt-out of receiving RhythmOne cookies. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the website may not work properly. If you opt out, your web browser will be associated with a generic "opt-out" cookie, which will prevent us from associating any non-personally identifiable information with your browser. Our "opt-out" cookie has a five-year expiration date. Keep in mind that participating in our opt-out program does not prevent you from seeing ads served by us, instead, the ads we serve to you will be generic and not be targeted to you based on your web surfing experiences. If you would like to opt out, please visit our Opt-Out page - <http://www.rhythmone.com/opt-out>. Alternatively, you may also choose not to use our website, you may also Opt-Out through the NAI’s Consumer Opt-Out Page - <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. These Opt-Outs are cookie-based, so you may need to opt out again (and set a new "opt-out" cookie) if you delete your cookies, lock cookies (including third party cookies), switch internet browsers, change computers or upgrade your web browser.

**Sensitive Health Information**

RhythmOne may use general health related information with customized advertising campaigns. General health-related information that is not based on a precise medical treatment or conditions is not considered "sensitive consumer information." This information can include, but is not limited to the following examples: acne, allergies, dental, vision, heartburn, cold and flu, sinus, headache, back pain, first aid, sore throat and cholesterol management. In addition, interest in subjects such as diet, nutrition, exercise, beauty, hair removal, health and fitness, as well as vitamins and supplements are not considered “sensitive consumer information”.

**P3P**

The Platform for Privacy Preferences (P3P) provides a way for ad networks and websites to publish their privacy policies in a machine-readable syntax. An ad network or website will deploy P3P in order to make its privacy practices more accessible to the site's visitors. A visitor's web browser can download the machine-readable privacy statements, and compare the contents of those statements to the user's preferences. This way, the user's browser can automatically notify the user when they visit a site whose practices match the user's preferences or warn the user if the practices and preferences don't match. RhythmOne has incorporated this technology in its ad servers. Our syntax reflects our current privacy policy.

**Cookies**

RhythmOne uses cookies to improve your web browsing experience. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer for the purpose of identifying your web browser. We use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on tour computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience with the website. When you are served a RhythmOne ad, RhythmOne assigns various information in a cookie on ads you've seen, information on sites you've visited and activities performed to your computer browser. We do this to understand the way a user responds to the ads we deliver. For example, this information lets us keep track of how many times you view an ad we distribute. Likewise, the cookie can help make sure you do not see the same ad over and over - thus enhancing your online Web viewing experience.

RhythmOne collects this information via our technology and it may be stored for up to 2 years for the purpose of analyzing campaign results, ensuring that our technology is functioning properly, and preventing fraud across our sites. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our website or our member sites. You can set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our website / service though your access to some functionality and areas of our website / service may be restricted. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser's help menu for more information.

**Disclosure**

RhythmOne uses the information we collect to improve, support and provide our advertising, measurement and reporting services. To do so more effectively, we have associated browsers and devices accessing our services to provide better and more consistent experiences to users. Examples include:

  * Serving and selecting ads – We use the information we have to find and match appropriate audiences to advertiser campaigns and to customize the ad served to your browser or device. We may also decide to show an ad based on things you may be interested in, or request from our advertising and agency customers who decide to show ads to a particular audience, sometimes using the information we have. We also use the information to optimize ad delivery, such as the frequency and order in which ads are displayed.
  * Measurement – We use the information we have to measure and understand the effectiveness of ads served across browsers and devices. This includes measuring interactions with advertisements and advertisers’ websites, apps and stores by analyzing information such as clicks or other interactions with ads, visits to websites or apps linked to from ads.
  * Improvement of Services – We use the information we have to support our services through activities such as infrastructure monitoring and internal maintenance, analyzing how our services are used, research and development, and billing. We may also use the information we have to maintain, protect, improve and develop our and our related companies’ services.
  * Protection of you, ourselves, and others – We may use information to detect, prevent, investigate and address fraud and other unauthorized or illegal activity.
  * Support and Inquiry – We may use the information provided to respond to inquiries and to provide customer and user support.

**RhythmOne’s Use of Cross-Application and Cross-Device Technology**

We and/or our customers may collect information about your activity across multiple unaffiliated third-party mobile applications. We may share this information with our customers in order to help them predict the types of ads that may be relevant to you and to display advertising to you accordingly. This information may also be combined with a mobile advertising identifier. To opt out of such practices, please see the Third-Party Measurement Services below and the Opting Out of Cookies section above.

We and/or our customers may use technology that establishes connections among related devices (such as mobile devices and desktop computers) both in order to deliver advertising that may be more relevant to you, as well as for analytics and reporting purposes. This means that information about your use of websites or applications on one of your devices may be combined with information from your other devices.

We may also partner with third parties to provide such cross-device technology to our customers, and in doing so we may share anonymous identifiers with those third parties in order to make connections among related devices. We may also use your device’s IP address to infer connections among related devices within the same household. To opt out of RhythmOne’s use of such technologies for each web browser and on each of your devices, please follow the instructions for opting out in both web browsers and mobile applications, as described in the Third-Party Measurement Services below and Opting Out of Cookies section above.

**Third-Party Measurement Services**

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company and service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

Visitors to the RythymOne website may be subject to data collection by third-parties for the purposes of serving interest-based advertising, based on browsing behavior. To Opt-Out on interest-based advertising, please visit the DAA Website - <http://www.aboutads.info/>.

Although certain RhythmOne technology honors “do not track” (DNT) signals and similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers or mobile device operating systems, RhythmOne is not responsible, and shall not be liable, for the acts of third parties, such as ad networks, with respect to such third parties’ tracking policies.

**Credit Cards**

When credit card data is required for services, we protect your credit card information using industry standard SSL encryption whenever card data is transmitted to us and when sending your credit card information to our credit card processor. While in our possession, your credit card number is protected with asymmetric encryption to keep it secure.

**Security**

We implement appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect your personal information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

**Merger or Acquisition**

If RhythmOne is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or we will post a notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Customer Testimonials**

With a user’s consent we post customer testimonials on our website which may contain personal information such as the customer’s name.

**No Information from Minors**

You must be at least 18 years of age to use the website. RhythmOne’s websites, products, and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children under the age of 13. With respect to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), RhythmOne does not knowingly collect personal information from nor employ or offer targeting towards children under the age of 13. If you believe your child, who is under the age of 13, has provided RhythmOne with personal information or registered at one of RhythmOne’s websites, please contact us at [privacy@rhythmone.com](mailto:privacy@rhythmone.com), and we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our records.

**International Transfer**

Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, we transfer your personal information to the United States and processes it there. We have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Notice. These include implementing the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses for transfers of personal information between our group companies, which require all group companies to protect personal information they process from the EEA in accordance with European Union data protection law.

Our Standard Contractual Clauses can be provided on request. We have implemented similar appropriate safeguards with our third party service providers and partners and further details can be provided upon request.

**Retention**

We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax or accounting requirements).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymise it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**Your data protection rights**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you have the following data protection rights:

  * If you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting Us” heading below.
  * In addition, you can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting Us” heading below.
  * You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing e-mails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing (such as postal marketing or telemarketing), then please contact us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting Us” heading below.
  * Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. Contact details for data protection authorities in the European Economic Area are available here - <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm>.
  * We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

**Notifications of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Any such modifications become effective upon your continued access to and/or use of the website five (5) days after we first post the changes on the website or otherwise provide you with notice of such modifications.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions, concerns or requests please contact us at [privacy@RhythmOne.com](mailto:privacy@rhythmone.com).

The data controller of your personal information is RhythmOne, LLC.

**RadiumOne Privacy Policy**

**Last updated:** May 24, 2018

RadiumOne is a digital advertising company and a wholly-owned subsidiary of RhythmOne plc. We value the privacy of consumers (“ **Users** ”, “ **you** ”, “ **your** ”) who visit our websites at [https://po.st](https://po.st/), or [http://radiumone.co.uk](http://radiumone.co.uk/) (the “ **Sites** ”) as well as other websites and mobile applications where our technology is enabled (together, the “ **Platform** ”). In this Privacy Notice we use the terms “ **RadiumOne** ”, “ **our** ”, “ **us** ”, and “ **we** ” to refer to R1Demand, LLC; RadiumOne UK Ltd.; and our affiliates.

The RadiumOne technology (the “ **Technology** ”) gathers User information from the Platform to optimize the delivery of digital advertising to Users. We use the information that we collect about you in connection to our advertising services to tailor advertising to you more effectively and for statistical reporting and analytics purposes, as further explained in the section “How We Use and Disclose Information” below. When we provide our advertising services under a contract with one of our clients for running campaigns on their behalf, we use the information that we collect about you for the purpose of providing the service for which the client has engaged us.

The purpose of this Privacy Notice is to explain what information we gather, how we use it, what we do to protect it, and your choices regarding how we gather and use information about you.

If you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Notice or practices, please see the “Contact Us” section below. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

**About Our Advertising Services**

RadiumOne provides online display, mobile, video, and social advertising services. In order to provide our services, we buy advertising space from hundreds of websites and mobile applications around the world and resell it in targeted packages to advertisers and agencies (“ **Targeted Advertising** ”). Targeted Advertising is displayed (a) on the browsers of devices such as computers, laptops, tablets or smartphones or (b) inside mobile applications. Users benefit from Targeted Advertising by receiving advertisements (“ **ads** ”) which are more interesting and relevant than untargeted ads, while advertisers benefit through the more efficient delivery of ads to interested Users.

Targeted Advertising is based on data that does not directly identify you and is collected from your devices as described below in “What Information We Collect”. Data used in Targeted Advertising may range from your (i) interests, (ii) similarities to other Users, (iii) general demographic information, and (iv) general geographic location. This non directly identifiable information is also known as pseudonymous data and may be used to classify Users who are most likely to respond to an ad. We do not intentionally collect information that identifies you (such as your name, address, phone number, or email address), and we prohibit our partners from sharing this information with us.

**What Information We Collect**

The information we collect falls into two categories – **Browser-Based Data** and **Mobile App-Based Data**.

For information about opting out from the collection of Browser-Based Data and Mobile App-Based Data, please visit our Opt Out page by clicking [here](https://radiumone.com/opt/).

_Browser-Based Data_

·       Cookies. Many websites use cookies to improve the User experience, and we use cookies in connection with our Technology. When you visit our Site or another website or page that displays one of our targeted ads or contains our pixel tags (also called clear gifs or web beacons), we may send one or more cookies (small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters) to your browser. Cookies enable us to store a RadiumOne User browser ID that is used for matching certain information that we collect via the browser. For more information about the types of cookies that we use, the purposes for which we use them and how you can opt out, click [here](https://radiumone.com/use-of-cookies/).

·       Ad Serving and Web Navigation Information. We may collect browser-based information regarding how you use the Platform and how you interact with the ads that the Platform displays (together, “ **Ad Serving and Web Navigation Information** ”). This Ad Serving and Web Navigation Information may include the following: (i) technographic data related to the browser, operating system, and device, such as the name and version of your browser, (ii) connection data (such as the device’s current IP address), (iii) the current website visited, (iv) the website visited before the current website, (v) search terms, (vi) the date and time of the website visit. (vii) whether the User has clicked on the ad of a RadiumOne advertiser, visited this advertiser’s website, or undertaken a transaction with this advertiser.

·       Po.st Information. Developers of Web sites may choose to implement our Po.st technology, which facilitates the sharing of Web content. When you use the Po.st services, we may receive Ad Serving and Web Navigation Information, including the URL content shared by a user (together, the “Po.st Information”). We can also discern which channel was used for sharing or receiving content (e.g. a social network or email). In addition, if you use Po.st to send an URL link to another user, and the user clicks on the sent URL link, we may also receive Ad Serving and Web Navigation information related to this user.

·       RadiumOne Engage Information. Developers of Web sites may choose to implement our RadiumOne Engage technology, which facilitates in-game advertising. When you use RadiumOne Engage advertising services, we may receive Ad Serving and Web Navigation Information, including (i) information about the game in which the advertising offer was placed, (ii) whether the User has clicked on the advertising offer, and (iii) whether the advertising offer was completed by the User (together, the “RadiumOne Engage Information”).

_Mobile Application-Based Data_

·       Device IDs. If you are using the Platform via a mobile application, we may use the Apple IFA, Android Advertiser ID, or other device information that uniquely identifies a mobile device (collectively, “ **Device IDs** ”) in order to match certain information that we collect via the mobile application.

·       Ad Serving Information. We may collect mobile-application-based information about how you interact with the ads that the Platform displays (together, “ **Ad Serving Information** ”). This Ad Serving Information may include the following: whether the User has (i) clicked on the ad of a RadiumOne advertiser, (ii) installed this advertiser’s application, or (iii) undertaken a transaction with this advertiser inside the downloaded application.

·       API or SDK Information. Developers of mobile applications may choose to implement our application programming interfaces (“ **APIs** ”) and software development kits (“ **SDKs** ”), such as RadiumOne Connect, which delivers push messages to consumers and provides developers with mobile analytics, geo-fencing capabilities, and advertising campaign attribution; and RadiumOne Engage, which delivers advertisements within mobile gaming applications (together, the “ **RadiumOne Software** ”). When a User accesses an application that implements the RadiumOne Software, we may collect certain User data, including: (i) technographic data related to the device (such as Apple IFA or Android Advertiser ID, device model, and operating system), (ii) information related to the application that implements the API or SDK (such as the version of the third party application, the SDK or the API being used), (iii) certain information relating to the applications installed on a mobile device (such as a list of the applications installed on the device), (iv) connection data (such as the IP address and mobile country or network code used to access the API or SDK), and (v) various data relating to the User (such as latitude and longitude, language preferences, or self-reported demographic data, including age, income, education or ethnicity).

·       iBeacons. We may collect information about your location through the use of iBeacon technology, an indoor positioning system that can notify nearby smartphones or other devices of their presence.

_Other Sources of Information_

·       We may acquire, use or re-sell to our self-service clients information from third party sources that may be used as is or in combination with Browser-Based Data and Mobile App-Based Data to optimize the delivery of digital advertising to Users. We require these third party sources to comply with applicable legal and industry standards.

·       We collect personal information from Web site visitors who sign up for our newsletter or submit their contact information. We do not use this information to deliver Targeted Advertising. Please see the section below entitled “RadiumOne Site Privacy Practices” for more details.

In providing our advertising services, RadiumOne collects information for and on behalf of its Clients and, to the extent that it processes personal information, RadiumOne has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal information it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients. If you wish to access, correct, amend, port or delete inaccurate personal information you should direct your query to RadiumOne’s Client (the data controller). If you address such requests to us, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

**How We Use and Disclose Information**

How We Use and Disclose Information In General. RadiumOne uses the information collected by the Technology to tailor advertising to you more effectively. The aim is to show you ads in which you are more likely to be interested. We do this by comparing the information in a pseudonymized User profile against our selection of ad campaigns and choosing the most relevant ad for you. Data used in your User profile may range from your (i) interests, (ii) similarities to other Users, (iii) general demographic information, and (iv) general geographic location. This data is collected from your devices as described above in “ _What Information We Collect.”_

·       Cross-App Advertising, Ad Delivery and Reporting. When you use a mobile device, we may use the information collected by the Technology regarding your use of the apps on your device to deliver Targeted Advertising based on the interests that we infer from your use of the mobile apps on the device (“ **Cross-App Advertising** ”). We may also use the information collected about the device for the purpose of delivering ads or providing related services such as delivering ads on the basis of a particular time of the day, optimizing the placement, performance, reach and frequency of our ads, and for statistical reporting and analytics purposes (“ **Ad Delivery and Reporting** ”).

·       Please note that we do not sell or transfer ownership of Browser-Based Data and Mobile App-Based Data to third parties.

**Legal basis for processing personal information (EEA Users only)**

If you are a User from the European Economic Area, our or our customer's legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect personal information from you only (i) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights, or (iii) where we have your consent to do so.

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information).

If we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), this interest will normally be to operate our Technology and communicating with you as necessary to provide our services to you and for our legitimate commercial interest, for instance, when responding to your queries, improving our Technology, undertaking marketing, or for the purposes of detecting or preventing illegal activities. We may have other legitimate interests and if appropriate we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided under the “Contact Us” heading below.

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

We may share information, including personal information collected via our Site, with trusted third parties that provide services for RadiumOne such as hosting and Internet connectivity. We may also share pseudonymous information with business partners in order to enhance our products and services. These third parties are prohibited from using the information we provide for purposes other than performing the services we prescribe. If you do not want us to share your information with these third parties, please contact us at [privacy@radiumone.com](mailto:privacy@radiumone.com).

**Opting-Out**

_Browser-Based Data Collection_

You can opt out from receiving RadiumOne Targeted Advertising based on data collected via your browser by doing one of the following:

·       Visiting our Opt Out page by clicking [here](https://radiumone.com/opt/). Please note that if you disable all cookies via your browser settings (see below), change the browser on the device from which you opted out of RadiumOne Targeted Advertising, or use a different device, you will need to opt out again from receiving cookies.

·       Visiting opt outs of standards bodies. RadiumOne is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (“ **NAI** ”), the Digital Advertising Alliance (“ **DAA** ”), the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (“ **DAAC** ”), the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance (“ **EDAA** ”), the Internet Advertising Bureau (“ **IAB** ”), and JICWEBS DTSG and adheres to each organization’s principles (the NAI Codes of Conduct, the DAA Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising, the Canadian Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioural Advertising, the EDAA Principles, IAB Europe’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising, and the JICWEBS DTSG Good Practice Principles, respectively). You can opt-out of RadiumOne Targeted Advertising based on data collected via your browser by using (a) the NAI’s opt-out tool, which can be found [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/); (b) the DAA’s opt-out tool, which can be found [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/); (c) the DAAC’s opt-out tool, which can be found [here](http://youradchoices.ca/choices/); or (d) the EDAA’s opt-out tool, which can be found [here](http://youronlinechoices.eu/).

When you opt out, we will stop (a) collecting information about your interests via your browser and (b) serving you Targeted Ads based on the data collected via your browser.

We will subsequently place a piece of data in your browser’s cookie that tells us that you have opted out of RadiumOne; it does not contain any data about you except for the fact that you have opted out. We need this cookie in place so that we know not to collect information about your interests and serve you interest-based targeted ads in the future.

_Mobile Application-Based Data Collection_

You can opt out from receiving Targeted Advertising based on data collected via your mobile applications by following your mobile device maker’s most current published instructions, such as the examples below (current as of the date of this version of our Privacy Policy):

**Android**  
Open the Google Settings app on your device

Select  **Ads**

**iOS**

Devices with iOS 6 and above use Apple’s Advertising Identifier. To learn more about limiting ad tracking using this identifier, visit the Settings menu on your device as follows:

_iOS 7 or higher –  _Choose  **Settings > Privacy > Advertising**

_iOS 6 –  _Choose  **Settings > General > About > Advertising**

Please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices) for an even more comprehensive and up-to-date description of how to opt out from your particular device.

When you opt out, we will stop (a) collecting information about your interests via your mobile applications and (b) serving you Targeted Ads based on the data collected via your mobile applications.

Please note that opting out of either Browser-Based or Mobile Application-Based Data Collection does not mean you will not see ads online from RadiumOne or other digital advertising companies, but only that RadiumOne will not tailor ads based on your interests.

**Data Retention**

RadiumOne uses Browser-Based Data and Mobile App-Based Data for Targeted Advertising for no more than 13 months. We maintain ad server log data and stored data for a period of up to 18 months in order to comply with audits, court order or law enforcement inquiries. After 18 months, all of the stored data is destroyed. Summarized data is kept indefinitely. Summarized data is aggregated statistical data (impressions, clicks, and conversions) used for financial reporting purposes. If we hold personal information about you as described in the “ _RadiumOne Site Privacy Practices_ ” section below, we will only keep it for as long as it is necessary for the purposes of (a) collecting and processing it and (b) complying with our legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our agreements.

**International Transfers**

Where it is transferred internationally, we have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy. These include implementing the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses for transfers of personal information between our group companies, which require all group companies to protect personal information they process from the EEA in accordance with European Union data protection law and self-certifying to the EU-US Privacy Shield as explained below.

Our Standard Contractual Clauses can be provided on request. We have implemented similar appropriate safeguards with our third party service providers and partners and further details can be provided upon request.

**Your data protection rights**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you have the following data protection rights:

  * If you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting Us” heading below.
  * In addition, you can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting Us” heading below.
  * You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time.  You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing e-mails we send you.  To opt-out of other forms of marketing (such as postal marketing or telemarketing), then please contact us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting Us” heading below.
  * Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time.  Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. Contact details for data protection authorities in the European Economic Area are available here - http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm .

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. As explained above, it may be for our client to respond to your request to exercise a data protection right.

**Security**

We put in place appropriate technical and organizational measures to preserve the integrity and security of User information and to prevent the unauthorized or unlawful processing of personal information and the accidental loss, destruction, or damage to personal information. These measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store data.

**In the Event of Merger or Sale**

In the event that RadiumOne is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. With regard to any personal information we collect via the Sites as described in the “RadiumOne Site Privacy Practices” section below, we will notify you via email and/or prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Children’s Privacy**

RadiumOne’s websites, products, and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children under the age of 13. With respect to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), RadiumOne does not knowingly collect personal information from nor employ or offer targeting towards children under the age of 13. If you believe your child, who is under the age of 13, has provided RadiumOne with personal information or registered at one of RadiumOne’s websites, please contact us at [privacy@radiumone.com](mailto:privacy@radiumone.com), and we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our records.

**RadiumOne Site Privacy Practices**

_Personal Information_

The Site is generally intended for use by businesses, advertisers, and potential partners interested in learning more about RadiumOne.

You may provide to RadiumOne the following personal information:

·       Contact Information such as name, email address, and phone number;

·       Business Information such as your job title and company name.

We use this information to:

·       Fulfill your requests;

·       Contact you regarding your inquiries;

·       Send you newsletters;

·       Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products;

·       Send you requested product and service information.

We do not use your personal information for any other purpose other than responding to your request. We do not share your personal information with other organizations without your express consent, except as set out in this Privacy Policy.

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, port or delete it by contacting us at [privacy@radiumone.com](mailto:privacy@radiumone.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe and in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may opt out by following the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of each communication.

_Tracking Technologies_

We use the following tracking technologies to optimize the Site for visitors and monitor your use of the Site.

_Performance and functionality cookies_.  
Description: These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of our website but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality (like videos) may become unavailable.

Who serves them: Vimeo (www.vimeo.com)

_Analytics and customization cookies._.

Description: These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our websites are being used or how effective are marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our Sites for you.

Who serves them: Google (www.google.com), Leadlander (www.leadlander.com), Marketo (www.marketo.com), ScorecardResearch (www.scorecardresearch.com)

**Disclosure by Legal Necessity**

RadiumOne may disclose your personal information if: (i) required by law, lawful request by public authorities (including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements), or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with applicable laws; (ii) we believe, in good faith, that such action is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; or (iii) such action is necessary to protect our, our Users’ or third parties’ rights. In such circumstances we may disclose your personal information to public authorities, law enforcement agencies, regulatory organizations, courts or other public authorities.

**Data Transfer**

The Site is hosted in the United States of America. If you choose to use the Site from other regions of the world, then please note that if you provide to us personal information when using the Site, you are transferring your personal information outside of those regions to the United States. We may also transfer to the United States of America, Singapore and Australia information collected in connection with our advertising services. We will protect personal information in all such transfers as described in this Privacy Policy. If you are located in the European Union, we will take reasonable steps to comply with applicable legal requirements to ensure an adequate level of protection of personal information that we transfer to countries outside of the European Union such as entering into Standard Contractual Clauses or relying upon the EU-US Privacy Shield.

**EU-U.S. Privacy Shield**

When we process any personal information originating from the European Union (EU) in the USA, RadiumOne participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from EU member countries. RadiumOne has certified that for all personal information received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, it will adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfers, Security, Data Integrity & Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s [Privacy Shield List](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list).

RadiumOne is responsible for the processing of personal information it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf, such as a service provider. Under the Privacy Shield, RadiumOne will remain liable if its third-party service providers process your personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles, unless we prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

With respect to personal information received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, RadiumOne is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

Residents of the EU who believe that their personal information has not been processed in compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles may raise their complaint in the following ways:

1.     You can contact RadiumOne directly using the details in the “Contact Us” section below. We will respond to your complaint within 45 days of receipt.

2.    We have further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield via TRUSTe, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive a timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by us, please contact TRUSTe (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

3.     Further, your complaint can be made or referred to the U.S. Department of Commerce or the Federal Trade Commission for further investigation.

4.    For residual disputes that cannot be resolved by the methods above, you may be able to invoke a binding arbitration process under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint), you may invoke binding arbitration. To find out more about the Privacy Shield’s binding arbitration scheme, please see <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our Site may also contain links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may be operated by companies not affiliated with RadiumOne. Linked websites may have their own privacy policies or notices, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content, your use, or the privacy notices of such websites.

**Social Media Applications**

Our Sites include Social Media Applications, such as the Facebook Like button or the Twitter Share button. These Applications may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Application to function properly. These Applications are either hosted by a third party. Your interactions with these Applications are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may need to change our Privacy Policy, in which case we will revise the “Last Updated” date. If we make material changes, we will notify you more directly, for example by posting a notification or message on the Site and/or one of our services or by emailing you prior to such changes taking effect. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently to stay informed of the latest modifications.

**Your Privacy Rights**

You may ask us at any time to provide you a copy of the personal information that we hold about you (if any) by emailing us at [privacy@radiumone.com](mailto:privacy@radiumone.com) or by writing to us using the contact details provided below. We may need to apply a charge to cover the cost of dealing with a request to provide you a copy of your personal information.

If you believe that we hold inaccurate personal information about you, please email us at [privacy@radiumone.com](mailto:privacy@radiumone.com) or write to us using the contact details below, so we can correct it. 

**Contact Us**

If you want to write to us regarding your privacy rights or have any questions, comments or complaints about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via [privacy@radiumone.com](mailto:privacy@radiumone.com) or write to us to one of the following addresses:

**If you are based in the United States or a country outside Europe:**  
R1Demand, LLC  
601 Montgomery St.  
16th Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94111  
USA

**If you are based in Europe or Australia:**  
RadiumOne UK Ltd.  
20 Garrick Street  
Covent Garden  
London, WC2E 9BT  
UK
